BRITT RAE JACK

Moriarty, NM 87035 • (505) 252-8571 • brittanyjack1989@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/britt-rae-jack • github.com/BrittRJack

Professional Summary

Driven professional with experience in project design and management.

Completed multiple independent projects including personal websites and database design. Interested in a career as a junior-level Web Developer.

Skills

- Data mapping
- Creative design
- HTML and CSS
- Data collection and analysis

- Intermediate Spanish
- SQL and databases
- Online marketing strategies
- JavaScript, PHP and Angular

Experience

Web Development Internship, 2018 to Current

CNM Deep Dive Coding Bootcamp – Albuquerque, NM

- Contributed to the development of a capstone project
- Developed wireframes, site maps and content in databases
- Developed object-oriented software in PHP
- Created a website that locates food trucks in local areas
- The food truck finder uses JavaScript API's and extensive back-end database structures in PHP and MYSQL
- Met with project managers on a weekly basis to provide a detailed project report and milestone updates
- Implemented Git for version control
- Wrote clean, clear and well-tested code for various projects

Youth Program Manager, 2013 to 2018

Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings Ltd – Miami, FL

- Trained and integrated new staff into the company's policies and procedures
- Conducted interviews for potential employees
- Was responsible for the safety and care of 1,100 children weekly
- Followed up with guests' concerns
- Kept detailed records and data from every voyage

English Language Teacher, 2009 to 2013

YMCA Inc – Augusta, MI

- Designed exams to test fluency in reading, writing, speaking and comprehension of the English language.
- Planned lessons for classroom of 30 students.
- Corresponded with students and parents through email, telephone or postal mail.
- Voted teacher of the year by the University of Santo Tomas, Colombia

Education

Certificate Of Completion: Full-Stack Software Development, 2018 **Deep Dive Coding Boot-camp** - Albuquerque, NM

Political Science, 2011

Orlando Technical College - Mid Florida Tech - Orlando, FL

Accomplishments

- Completed 450 hours of in class course work through Deep Dive Coding Boot-Camp
- Completed an additional 160 hours of at home assignments